A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Education and Public Policy Program (EPP), Office of the Arts, Program Files FA640
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1952-1970; XI
  - Pacific Northwest Library Association, 1961 (Box 39)
  - Policy and Discussions Papers, 1963 (Box 39)
  - Press, 1958 (Box 39)
  - San Francisco Palace of Fine Arts, 1960 (Box 39)
  - Scenic Design Program -- Background, 1962 (Box 39)
  - Scenic Design Program -- Correspondence, 1962 (Box 39)
  - Scenic Design Program -- Forms, 1961 (Box 39)
  - Scenic Design Program -- Grant Actions, 1965 (Box 39)
  - Scenic Design Program -- Grantees, 1962 (Box 39)
  - Scenic Design Program -- Nomination List and Forms (Box 39)
  - Scenic Design Program -- Nominees' Correspondence, 1962 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Music (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Consultants, 1958 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Correspondence, 1959 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Creative Writing, 1958 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Dance, undated (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Docket Items, 1964 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Outline Versions, 1958 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Outline -- Other Media (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Outline -- Propositional Statements (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Outline -- Theater Arts (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Outline -- Visual Arts (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Economic Support of Arts Collectively (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- W. McNeil Lowry European Reports, 1958-1960 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Pringle Case Study re: Pittsburgh, 1959 (Box 39)
  - Study of the Economic and Social Positions of the Artist and his Institutions in the United States -- Pringle Case Study re: Cincinnati, 1959 (Box 39)
  - Teachers of Composition (American), 1957 (Box 39)
  - Texas Foundations and Trust Funds, 1957 (Box 39)
  - Thesaurus Linguae Latinae, 1959 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Background and Planning, 1961-1962 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Art Institute of Chicago, 1961 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1961 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Docket Item and Budget, 1960 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Director, 1964 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Executive Committee Correspondence, 1963 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Executive Committee Minutes, 1964 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Advisory Board, 1961-1964 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- Participating Theaters, 1961-1962 (Box 39)
  - Theater Communications Group -- General Correspondence and Inquiries, 1961 (Box 39)
  - National Music Council -- Cid W. Waldrop's Field Reprints, 1958-1961 (Box 40)
  - Performing Arts, Grants for, 1966 (Box 59)
  - Philanthropic Foundations, 1957-1962 (Box 59)
  - Patman Investigation re: Tax Exempt Foundations, 1954-1963 (Box 59)
  - Pittsburgh, University of -- Grants FY 1957-1968, 1956-1968 (Box 59)
  - Population Vol. II -- Grantee Lists, 1963-1964 (Box 59)
  - Population, Family Planning, Reproductive Biology -- Grant Lists, Reports, Notes, 1962-1966 (Box 59)
  - Private Organizations, [1968] (Box 59)
  - Professional Schools, Grants to, 1959-1965 (Box 59)
  - Program Review Session -- Draft Report, Sep 1956 (Box 59)
  - Ford Foundation Grants and Programs, 1956-1967 (Box 59)
  - Program Review -- Charts and Worksheets re: Programs over the last 10 years, 1960 (Box 59)
  - Public Affairs, 1961-1965 (Box 59)
  - Public Opinion, Survey of, 1961-1965 (Box 59)
  - Religious Affiliations, 1968-1969 (Box 59)
  - Research and Analysis, Letters and Memoranda regarding, 1964-1966 (Box 59)
  - Research Requests, 1966 (Box 59)
  - Science and Engineering -- Ford Foundation Grants, 1961-1970 (Box 59)
  - Social Sciences, 1961-1967 (Box 59)
  - Social Science Research Council, Grants to, 1957-1969 (Box 59)
  - Sociological Associations, American and International, 1962 (Box 59)
  - Special Programs in Education, 1966 (Box 59)
  - Specific Disciplines and General Fields, 1961-1965 (Box 59)
  - State Booklets, Master File re: Foundation Grants, 1957-1965 (Box 59)
  - Select States, FY 1967-1968 Grants to (Box 59)
  - Alaska -- Grants, 1969 (Box 59)
  - Alabama -- Grants, 1962-1970 (Box 59)
  - Arizona -- Grants, 1959-1964 (Box 59)
  - Arkansas -- Grants, 1962-1970 (Box 59)
  - California -- Grants, 1961-1969 (Box 59)
  - Colorado -- Grants, 1959-1970 (Box 59)
  - Connecticut -- Grants, 1959-1965 (Box 59)
  - Delaware -- Grants, 1965 (Box 59)
  - District of Colombia -- Grants, 1965 (Box 59)
  - Florida -- Grants, 1964-1970 (Box 59)
  - Georgia -- Grants, 1962-1970 (Box 59)
  - Hawaii -- Grants, 1965-1968 (Box 59)
  - Idaho -- Grants, 1963-1965 (Box 59)
  - Illinois -- Grants, 1957-1969 (Box 59)
  - Indiana -- Grants, 1957-1970 (Box 59)
  - Iowa -- Grants, 1964 (Box 59)
  - Kansas -- Grants, 1964 (Box 59)
  - Press Relations -- Press Releases re: Fellowship Awards for Business Administration and Economics, 1958-1959 (Box 59)
- American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires, 1961-1972; XII
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- American-Brooklyn (1/4), 1961-1971 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- American-Brooklyn (2/4), 1961-1971 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- American-Brooklyn (3/4), 1961-1971 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- American-Brooklyn (4/4), 1961-1971 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- Buffalo-Dallas (1/3), 1965-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- Buffalo-Dallas (2/3), 1965-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- Buffalo-Dallas (3/3), 1965-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- Denver-Hartford (1/3), 1962-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- Denver-Hartford (2/3), 1962-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- Denver-Hartford (3/3), 1962-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires -- Honolulu-Jacksonville, 1964-1971 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires --Kalamazoo-Memphis, 1965-1971 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires --Milwaukee-New Orleans (1/2), 1963-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires --Milwaukee-New Orleans (2/2), 1963-1972 (Box 41)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires (N-O), 1961-1972 (Box 42)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires (P-R), 1961-1972 (Box 42)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires (R-S), 1961-1972 (Box 42)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires (Sa-Sy), 1961-1972 (Box 42)
  - American Symphony Orchestra Questionnaires (T-W), 1961-1972 (Box 42)
- Program Files, 1955-1977; XIII
  - American Operatic Repertoire -- Background and Correspondence, 1973 (Box 43)
  - American Operatic Repertoire -- Grant Actions -- Companies, 1961-1974 (Box 43)
  - American Operatic Repertoire -- Grant Actions -- Composers Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 43)
  - American Operatic Repertoire -- Press Releases, 1961-1965 (Box 43)
  - American Operatic Repertoire -- Extension, 1971-1974 (Box 43)
  - Archaeology -- Background, 1964-1969 (Box 43)
  - Archaeology -- Consultants, 1964-1967 (Box 43)
  - Archaeology -- Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 43)
  - Archaeology -- Forms, 1972 (Box 43)
  - Archaeology -- Grant Actions, 1968-1970 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Development Program -- Background, 1962-1963 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Development Program -- Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Development Program -- Grant Actions, 1967 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Society Inc. -- General, 1958-1962 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Society Inc. -- Collection of Data for Study, 1959-1960 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Society Inc. -- Regional Scholarship Program -- School of American Ballet, 1959-1965 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Society Inc. -- Regional Scholarship Program -- San Francisco Ballet School, 1959-1964 (Box 43)
  - Ballet Society Inc. -- Schools Visited, 1960-1961 (Box 43)
  - Civic Opera Program -- Background, 1963 (Box 43)
  - Civic Opera Program -- Correspondence, 1963 (Box 43)
  - Civic Opera Program -- Evaluation, 1970 (Box 43)
  - Civic Opera Program -- Grant Actions, 1964-1966 (Box 43)
  - Civic Opera Program -- Status Reports, 1970 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Background (1/2), 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Background (2/2), 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Consultants, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Forms, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Grant Actions, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Judges' Meetings and Auditions, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Judges' Correspondence, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Nominators, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Nominees, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Press Releases, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Statistics, 1971 (Box 43)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Background, 1958-1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Forms, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Grant Actions, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Judges' Correspondence, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Judges' Declinations, 1961 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Judges' Meeting, Apr 2-3, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Nominators' Correspondence, 1961 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Nominees' Correspondence, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Press Releases, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Statistics, 1963 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Beckwith, Robert S., 1968 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Boepple, Paul, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Dexter, John R., 1969 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Greenburg, Noah, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Hirt, Charles C., 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Hunter, George H., 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Morton, Ian A., 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Pinkham, Daniel R., Jr., 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Smith, Gregg, 1966 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Sokol, Thomas A., 1962 (Box 44)
  - Choral Directors Program -- Swan, Howard S., 1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Leon Fleisher, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Composers -- Elliot Carver, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Jacob Lateiner, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Denver Symphony Society, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Indiana State Symphony Society, Inc., 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Pittsburgh Symphony Society, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Background, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grant Actions, 1958 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Grantees, 1971 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Background, 1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Correspondence, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Forms, 1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grant Actions, 1962-1968 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Judges' Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Judges' Declinations, 1961-1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Judges' Meeting, Mar 1-2, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1962-1969 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Nominators' Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Nominees, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Participating Organizations, 1962-1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Press Releases, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Scheduling Correspondence A-L, 1962-1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Scheduling Correspondence M-Z, 1962-1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Statistical Data, 1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Allen and Thomson, 1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Beardslee and babbitt, 1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Graffman and Lees, 1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Gramm and Cumming, 1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Harth and Dello Joio, 1962-1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Istomin and Sessions, 1968 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Lateiner, Jacob, 1969 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Nelsova and Haieff, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Raskin and Laderman, 1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Sarfay and Rorem, 1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Sanofsky and Rosenthal (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Senofski and Rosenthal, 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Shirley and Perkinson, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Shumsky and Porter, 1963 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Simon and Fuleihan, 1962-1964 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Sorel and Mennin, 1965-1967 (Box 44)
  - Concert Soloists Program -- Grantees -- Starker and Harris, 1962-1965 (Box 44)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Forms, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Judges' Correspondence, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Judges' Meeting, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Nominators' Correspondence, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Nominees' Correspondence, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Press Releases and Fact Sheet, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Adele Addison, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Phyllis Curtin, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Joseph Fuchs, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Irene Jordan, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Seymour Lipkin, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- William Masselos, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Michael Rabin, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Leonard Rose, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Paul Creston, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Carlisle Floyd, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Lukas Foss, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Vittorio Giannini, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Leon Kirchner, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Walter Piston, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- William Schuman, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Harold S. Shapero, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Grantees -- Composers -- Ben Weber, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Participating Orchestras -- Atlanta Symphony Guild, Inc., 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Participating Orchestras -- Detroit Symphony Orchestra, Inc., 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Participating Orchestras -- Houston Symphony Society, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Participating Orchestras -- The Philharmonic Society of New York, Inc., 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Participating Orchestras -- the Seattle Symphony Orchestra, Inc., 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Participating Orchestras -- Southern California Symphony Association, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Participating Orchestras -- Symphony Society of San Antonio, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Background, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Correspondence, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Forms, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grant Actions, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Judges' Correspondence, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Judges' Meeting, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Correspondence with Nominators, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Press Releases and Fact Sheet, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Alswang-Rudolph, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Elder-stone, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Greenbie-Hiller, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Hays-Blake, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Izenour-Schweikher, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Kiesler, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Mielziner-Barnes, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Theater Design, Program For -- Grantees -- Schlanger-Oenslager, 1959 (Box 45)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Grantees, 1958 (Box 46)
  - Concert Artists, Program For -- Press Release, Letter re: Nominations, etc., 1958 (Box 46)
  - Concert Soloists, Program for -- Grantees -- Nominations, 1961 (Box 46)
  - Concert Soloists, Program for -- Press Release, List of Nominees, Summary, 1962 (Box 46)
  - Opera Singers, Program for -- Grantees, 1961-1962 (Box 46)
  - Opera Singers, Program for -- Record of Contracts, 1964 (Box 46)
  - Opera Singers, Program for -- Press Release, Participating Companies, Nominees, Finalists, etc., 1961-1962 (Box 46)
  - Purchase Program Museum Index, undated (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1962 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1963 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1964 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1965 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1966 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1967 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1968 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Program Book, 1969 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Evaluation Memorandum, 1974 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Evaluation Draft Report, 1970 (Box 46)
  - Administrative Interns, Program for -- Evaluation -- Background including Status Reports, 1969-1977 (Box 46)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Applicants First Year, 1959 (Box 47)
    See also Ford Foundation Project file D-22: Fellowship program for non-academic scholars in the creative arts (Studies in the Creative Arts); and Grant file 06090249 (PA60-249), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), “PROGRAM FOR STUDIES IN THE CREATIVE ARTS”.
  - Creative Arts Program -- Applicants, 1960 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Applicants, 1961 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Applicants, 1962 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Forms, 1963 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- General, 1959-1965 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Grant Actions, 1959-1965 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges First Year, 1960 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges Meeting First Year, 1960 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges Second Year, 1961 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges Meeting Second Year, 1961 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges Third Year, 1962 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges Meeting Third Year, 1962 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges Fourth Year, 1963 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Judges Meeting Fourth Year, 1963 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Press Releases, 1963 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Grantees A-H, 1963-1965 (Box 47)
    1959 Grantees include: Florence E. Day; Antal Dorati; Edward H. Dwight; Mark Epstein; Martin Friedman; Noah Greenberg; Louise E. Jefferson; Newell Jenkins; Norton Juster; Edward Kook; Walter McQuade; John Peter; James P. Powell; Philip R. Randall.
    1960 Grantees include: Dore Aston; Sol Babitz; Marie Farnsworth; Robert Forth; Douglass Howell; Paul Mills; Philip R. Randall (renewal); Mary Rasmussen; Charles Shackford; Lee Simonson; Chester Sprague.
    1961 Grantees include: Boris Aronson; Nathan Broder; Ebria Feinblatt; David Flaherty; Ann Parker and Avon Neal; Gordon Rogoff; Jane Powell Rosenthal (renewal); Pauline Sommons; Felice Stampfle; Ikuyo Tagawa; Edward N. Waters.
    1962 Grantees include: Wayne V. Andersen; Sol Babitz (renewal); Louisa Bellinger; Harold Clurman; Mark Epstein (renewal); Marie Farnsworth (renewal); David Flaherty (renewal);Yvonne Hackenbroch; Avon Neal (renewal); Ann Parker (renewal); Denise Restout; Bernard Rudofsky; Susan Sawitzky; Eleanor A. Sayre; Ben Schlanger; Dorothy G. Shepherd; Parker Tyler; Charlotte M. Ullman.
  - Creative Arts Program -- Grantees J-R, 1963-1965 (Box 47)
  - Creative Arts Program -- Grantees S-W, 1963-1965 (Box 47)
  - Creative Writers, Program for -- Letter to Nominators, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Creative Writers, Program for -- Nominating Form, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Creative Writers, Program for -- List of Nominators, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Creative Writers, Program for -- Confidential Inquiry Form, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- Letter to Nominators, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Concert Artists, Program for -- List of Nominees, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Directors, Program for -- Letter to Nominators, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Directors, Program for -- Letter to Nominators (second), 1958 (Box 47)
  - Directors, Program for -- Nominating Form, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Directors, Program for -- Letter to Nominees, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Nominations, 1958 (Box 47)
    See also Ford Foundation Project file C-620: Grants in Aid program for visual artists; and Grant files: 05900120 (PA59-120), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), PROGRAM FOR VISUAL ARTISTS; 06000084 (PA60-84), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), PROGRAM FOR VISUAL ARTISTS; and 06090071 (PA60-71), Foundation-Administered Project (FAP), PURCHASE PRIZES AWARDED IN CONNECTION WITH 1959 PROGRAM FOR VISUAL ARTISTS.
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Letter to Nominators, 1958 (Box 47)
  - Visual Artists, Program for -- Letter to Nominees, 1958 (Box 47)